Mario Luciano Bruno

510-386-2500 mbrunostem@gmail.com Washington, D.C.

Profile

I am a highly driven individual and have been working in education as a project manager for the past 6 years. I recently completed a Fullstack coding course via Georgia Tech, and I am looking to move my career in a new direction. I work well in collaborative environments, as well as taking on independent projects. I have a passion for learning new things, am quick to learn, and thrive off of constructive feedback.

Work Experience

2019 - Present. Rocketship Legacy Prep, Washington, D.C. STEM Fluency Manager

- Managing students' fluency and assessment data spreadsheets.
- Analyzing the data to maximize students' success by facilitating group and on-on-one tutor sessions.
- Assessing data trends from the students' online learning programs.
- Delivering analysis of data and action plans to administration.

2017 – 2019. Sherman Elementary School, San Francisco, Ca Computer Lab Teacher & Tech Liaison

- Project manager of the Digital Citizenship and Computer Science cohort.
- Crafting lesson plans in alignment with the Digital Citizenship and Computer Science cohort standards.
- Integrating educational technology (Ed Tech) into the computer lab.
- Collaborating to bring Ed Tech into homeroom classes.

2016 – 2017. Higher Ground, Oakland, Ca After-School Program Director

- Directing the daily operations of the after-school program.
- Curating a monthly enrichment activity calendar.
- Scheduling and coordinating any off-campus field trips.
- Managing all supply orders for the after-school program.

2015 – 2016. Pressed Juicery, Stanford, Ca Quality Assurance Supervisor

- Managing the quality assurance team and coordinating with the delivery drivers.
- Utilizing in-house software to input and track inventory data.
- Reviewing the inventory data my team submitted and correcting any discrepancies.
- Communicating any policy changes or announcements from corporate to my team.

Technical Skills

- Project Management
- General Management
- Data Entry & Analysis
- Google & Microsoft Applications
- JavaScript, React, & CSS

Education

2021 - 2022.	Georgia Tech Fullstack Bootcamp, Atlanta, Ga
2018 - 2019.	San Francisco City College, San Francisco, Ca
2012 - 2016.	Ohlone College, Fremont, Ca